<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days App</string>
    <string name="Tips1">Draw something using only 3 colors you wouldn’t normally pick.</string>
    <string name="Tips2">Sketch your breakfast, no matter how messy it is.</string>
    <string name="Tips3">Spend 10 minutes making random marks — don’t aim for a finished piece.</string>
    <string name="Tips4">Redraw a childhood drawing with your current skills.</string>
    <string name="Tips5">Pick an object nearby and draw it from 3 different angles.</string>
    <string name="Tips6">Create something entirely in silhouette form (just shapes, no details).</string>
    <string name="Tips7">Listen to a song and draw what it feels like.</string>
    <string name="Tips8">Use a timer — 5 minutes for a sketch, then stop. Repeat with new ideas.</string>
    <string name="Tips9">Try drawing with your non-dominant hand.</string>
    <string name="Tips10">Pick a random word from a book and illustrate it.</string>
    <string name="Tips11">Fill a page with only one type of texture or pattern.</string>
    <string name="Tips12">Combine two animals into one creature.</string>
    <string name="Tips13">Draw a scene using only straight lines.</string>
    <string name="Tips14">Redesign a character from your favorite movie or game.</string>
    <string name="Tips15">Make a comic strip with only 3 panels.</string>
    <string name="Tips16">Sketch in total darkness (don’t peek until you’re done).</string>
    <string name="Tips17">Paint or draw something entirely in shades of one color.</string>
    <string name="Tips18">Do a “draw your day” journal entry.</string>
    <string name="Tips19">Take a photo you like and turn it into a simplified line drawing.</string>
    <string name="Tips20">Pick a random household object and turn it into a fantasy weapon or gadget.</string>
    <string name="Tips21">Draw a famous landmark without looking at a reference — from memory.</string>
    <string name="Tips22">Start with a scribble, then turn it into a creature or character.</string>
    <string name="Tips23">Only draw with circles — no other shapes allowed.</string>
    <string name="Tips24">Doodle on top of a printed-out photo.</string>
    <string name="Tips25">Recreate a famous artwork in your own style.</string>
    <string name="Tips26">Sketch an object at extreme zoom (just a small detail of it).</string>
    <string name="Tips27">Make a collage of random shapes, then trace over it.</string>
    <string name="Tips28">Draw yourself as if you lived in a different time period.</string>
    <string name="Tips29">Create an artwork using only one continuous line.</string>
    <string name="Tips30">Choose your favorite from the month and make a polished, final version.</string>
</resources>